http://kadampa-center.org/privacy-policy

Kadampa Center
for the Practice of Tibetan Buddhism in the Gelugpa Tradition
His Holiness the 14th Dalai Lama
Main menu
HomeAbout UsOverviewWhat is Buddhism?Our Lineage and TeachersHis Holiness the 14th Dalai LamaLama Thubten YesheLama Thubten Zopa RinpocheGeshe GelekGeshe SangpoRobbie WatkinsVenerable Lhundub TendronStephanie SmithOur SanghaOur AltarBookstoreBookstore FAQsCan I make a purchase online?Can I special order a book?How do I know how much to pay for the books?How do I make a purchase?Is it appropriate to "sell" the dharma?So, what does happen to any money generated from the Bookstore?So, why should I buy books at the bookstore (instead of from Amazon or other places)?More About Our Bookstore TitlesNoteworthy Bookstore TitlesSample Bookstore TitlesVisiting the CenterOverviewFrequently Asked QuestionsStudent VisitsFor Out-of-Town VisitorsMembershipContact/Find UsCenter Management TeamBoard of DirectorsBudget and Financial ReportsDonate NowVolunteeringGroundsSpiritual ProgramSpiritual Program NotesIntroductory ProgramsBuddhism in a NutshellMeditation 101Sundays: Dharma for a Happy LifeBeginner ProgramsDiscovering BuddhismDiscovering Buddhism MaterialAbout PujasWhat to expect at a pujaWays to participate more deeply in pujasGuru puja with tsogMedicine Buddha PujaTara Practice NightSponsor a PujaIntermediate ProgramsHow to Get Enlightened: Lamrim Class with Geshe GelekBasic ProgramResources for Illness and DyingHoly DaysRetreatsLight of the Path Retreat 2021Light of the Path Retreat 2017Visiting TeachersVenerable Amy Miller Recordings of Teachings at Kadampa CenterVenerable Robina Courtin Online Teachings hosted by Kadampa Center June 1-7,2020Sangha Support and OfferingsOur AltarBuddha Statues for Your AltarFPMT-Related EventsKadampa StupaCharacteristics of a StupaKadampa Stupa CharacteristicsStupa ResourcesAbout the ArtistVows and OrdinationCare of Dharma MaterialsAdditional Buddhist ResourcesTibetan Names & MeaningsFamily ProgramFamily Program OverviewSunday MorningSunday Morning FAQsKadampa Family Dharma CampCommunityGet InvolvedMerit MakersOffer Service or In-Kind SupportProjectsInternational Merit Box ProjectPrison ProjectWho We ServeSupport the Prison ProjecteNewsletter ArchiveSpeaker/Group Visit RequestGalleriesOutreachOutreach EventsTriangle Interfaith AllianceRecordingsStreaming
You are hereHome
Privacy & Security Policy
We want you to know how we collect, use and protect information about our online customers.
Our Privacy Policy
Kadampa Center respects your right to privacy. We value our customers' trust. To insure your privacy, we only use customer information for order identification, customer service contact, or demographic analysis. We may need to contact customers by phone, postal mail, or email if questions arise regarding your order. Demographic analysis is done by kadampa-center.org only, and information is not shared with anyone not affiliated with Kadampa Center.
We do not send unsolicited or "spam" e-mail. Kadampa Center uses e-mail addresses to communicate with our users, to send information about your order, and newsletters.
We do not sell, rent, or lend any personal information about our customers to any third party. All information provided to us is kept in strict confidence.
Options our customers have
If you provide our Web site with your e-mail address, you may receive e-mails from us. If you do not want to receive marketing or promotional e-mails from our Web site, you can discontinue these e-mails by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.
What about links to and from other Web sites?
Our Web site may offer links to other sites. Other sites have their own policies regarding privacy. If you visit one of these sites, you may want to review the privacy policy on that site. In addition, you may have linked to our Web site through another site. In such cases the site you linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites to see how they collect and use this information.
Your consent
By using our Web site, you consent to our use of customer information as described in this online privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy so we encourage you to review it periodically.
Our commitment to Data Security
We have appropriate physical, electronic and procedural security safeguards to protect and secure the information we collect.
Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)
Our Web site uses 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to protect your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions.
When you use secure portions of our site or proceed to our online checkout, either a solid key or a locked padlock icon will appear in the lower right of your browser window. This icon insures that your transaction session is secured through SSL.
Our use of Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. Cookies allow us to provide features such as storage of items in your shopping bag between visits.
The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of our web site's best features, so we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Last updated October 18, 2012
5412 Etta Burke Court, Raleigh, NC 27606 USA
Tel (919) 859-3433
info@kadampa-center.org
Privacy Policy
Website Feedback
Copyright ©2020 The Kadampa Center
Affiliated with
